[{"answer": "Yes, somebody died.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Does somebody die?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "That was always my -- that was always my intention to become the new Piers Morgan.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Could you give me your thoughts on that?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "First of all, your read was impeccable.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Howard, it doesn't get better than that, does it?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "The Parents Television Council.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Parents, Teacher Council or something?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Is that right, Piers?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "And people say to me, what's their talent, and I guess they'll throw the same thing at you and say, all right, you're a good deejay but what else do you do, and the reality is you don't have to go to the sun to know it's hot, right?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it goes back to what I was saying before that, you know, I think a lot of times Howie and Sharon, you know, pick someone just to kind of annoy you.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Would you like to clarify that?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Yes, I would avoid Howie Mandell like the plague, would be my main advice to you .", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you have any advice for me?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I'm interviewing Claire Danes from \"Homeland \"who I think is one of the great acting talents in America right now.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Who's on next?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, it was an extraordinary effort, Piers, and perhaps, you know, on -- at one level it was nine years.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Mr. Crowley, what are your thoughts as the Iraq war ends?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Does that make the war in your view potentially an illegal conflict?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "ROWLEY: Well, you know, eight months ago I thought that Bradley Manning's treatment out of Brig in Quantico was a distraction and was actually undercutting the unnecessary prosecution.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What are your feelings about that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "What was really extraordinary about those three USO tours was that it was probably one of the most -- really probably -- I was profoundly, you know, changed by it.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Do they feel once it was clear the weapons of mass destruction didn't actually exist that it was a legitimate conflict?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Yes, I think -- I think that we have to as a people reclaim a certain kind of rationality when it comes to candidates.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "It is disappointing if Donald Trump really doesn't run that we could miss out on President Trump, isn't it?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "He's stellar.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Because Herman Cain was, from a comedic point of view, gold dust, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, zany is not a word I'd use for Newt Gingrich.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Only to really examine whether you feel being accused of being too zany, and this seems certainly an appropriate question for you, Lewis, one of the zaniest man in America, is being zany a criteria for not being taken seriously as a president?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Um, we're both phony blonds.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "How much of this -- and I really want the answer to be a lot -- how much of her is in you?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I just finished filming.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "The more successful the show has got, that that kind of issue becomes very, oh, ok, better be careful here?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "It's wonderful.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "How exciting is that for you from an acting point?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "This won't take long.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "If you're about to do it, OK, what would you want the other person to say, like right before?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "No, for real.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Don't I know you?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Terrifying?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "No, that's not true.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "ANES: It wasn't overtly offered to me.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well, I had a very -- I had a steady boyfriend at the time.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What else did you get into?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Do you love it?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Paparazzi are difficult.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Have you got better at dealing with that?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "It's a machine I just made!", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "That was an intense run.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "You've racked up some awards, haven't you?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Um, no.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Was it love at first British sight?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Yes, two years.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "And you've been married what, two years now?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Your toes?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "It's miserable.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Who gets the more jealous about the love scenes the other ones have to do?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "It is, isn't it?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Yes -- eventually, I'd love that.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Do you want to yet?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Look at you, pokey, pokey McGee.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Getting broody yet?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "We'll see.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "See how I used that shamelessly?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "We're doing another season.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "ORGAN: So what's left, \"Homeland,\" presumably there will be another series of \"Homeland,\" right?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, yes.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Oh, you are?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111215pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "See how it easy it is to get that stuff out there?", "qSentId": 725}]